Guide to the Horace Walpole Collection
The Lewis Walpole Library
- Horace Walpole's Correspondence, 1725-1797; Series I; 12
  - Mann, Sir Horatio, 1st Baronet *
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 May 23 NS (Box 15, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 47-50.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 May 30 NS (Box 15, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 51-54.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Jun 3 NS (Box 15, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 54-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Jun 10 NS (Box 15, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 58-64.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Jun 17 NS (Box 15, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 64-69.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Jun 24 NS (Box 15, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 69-73.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1741 Jun 29 NS (Box 15, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 74-77.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Jul 1 NS (Box 15, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 77-84.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, Circa 1741 Jul 5 NS (Box 15, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 84-85.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Jul 8 NS (Box 15, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 86-87.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Jul 15 NS (Box 15, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 88.
    - From Horace Mann and Antonio Cocchi, letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Jul 18 NS (Box 15, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 89-90.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1741 Jul 19 NS (Box 15, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 91-93.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Jul 23 NS (Box 15, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 93-96.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Jul 30 NS (Box 15, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 96-99.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Aug 6 NS (Box 15, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 99-103.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Aug 12 NS (Box 15, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 103-6.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Aug 21 NS (Box 15, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 106-12.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Aug 22 NS (Box 15, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 113-15.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Aug 27 NS (Box 15, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 115-18.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Sep 2 NS (Box 15, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 118-23.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole, 1741 Sep 5 NS (Box 15, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 124-27.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Sep 10 NS (Box 15, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 127-31.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Sep 17 NS (Box 15, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 131-38.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Sep 24 NS (Box 15, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 143-48.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Oct 1 NS (Box 15, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 148-53.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Oct 8 NS (Box 15, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 153-59.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Oct 15 NS (Box 15, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 160-63.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Nov 11 NS (Box 15, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 178-83.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Nov 19 NS (Box 15, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 192-96.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Nov 26 NS (Box 15, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 197-201.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Dec 2 NS (Box 15, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 201-8.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Dec 10 NS (Box 15, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 213-18.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Dec 17 NS (Box 15, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 222-27.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Dec 19 NS (Box 15, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 227-29.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1741 Dec 24 NS (Box 15, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 235-42.
      With enclosure: Letter from Vernaccini to Craon, 22 Dec. 1741.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jan 10 NS (Box 15, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 258-64.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jan 16 NS (Box 15, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 264-69.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jan 21 NS (Box 15, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 280-86.
      With enclosure: Lists of the English and Spanish fleets.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jan 28 NS (Box 15, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 286-94.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Feb 3 NS (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 303-10.
      With enclosures: Copy of Giovanni Maria del Fantasia's letter to Craon, 29 Jan. 1742 NS; Copy of Maricone's letter to Braitwitz, 31 Jan. 1742 NS; Copy of Braitwitz's letter to Mann, 3 Feb. 1742 NS.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Feb 6 NS (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 311-13.
      With enclosures: Copy of Maricone's letter to Braitwitz, 31 Jan. 1742 NS; Copy of Braitwitz's letter to Mann, 3 Feb. 1742 NS.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Feb 11 NS (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 313-18.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Feb 18 NS (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 321-28.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Mar 5 NS (Box 16, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 340-43.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Mar 11 NS (Box 16, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 348-52.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Mar 18 NS (Box 16, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 360-62.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Mar 25 NS (Box 16, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 367-69.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Apr 1 NS (Box 16, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 369-72.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Apr 8 NS (Box 16, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 379-82.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Apr 17 NS (Box 16, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 387-89.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Apr 22 NS (Box 16, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 393-96.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 May 7 NS (Box 16, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 402-9.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 May 15 NS (Box 16, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 412-18.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 May 20 NS (Box 16, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 421-25.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 May 27 NS (Box 16, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 426-28.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jun 3 NS (Box 16, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 432-34.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jun 17 NS (Box 16, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 442-47.
      With enclosure: Fictitious letter to M. de Thun.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jun 20 NS (Box 16, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 447-50.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jun 24 NS (Box 16, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 453-56.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jul 1 NS (Box 16, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 460-65.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jul 8 NS (Box 16, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 470-74.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jul 15 NS (Box 16, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 480-84.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jul 22 NS (Box 16, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 488-91.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Jul 29 NS (Box 16, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 17, p. 497-501.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Aug 5 NS (Box 16, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 1-7.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Aug 12 NS (Box 16, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 9-14.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Aug 19 NS (Box 16, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 14-18.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Aug 26 NS (Box 16, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 26-29.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Sep 10 NS (Box 16, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 37-43.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Sep 16 NS (Box 16, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 44-46.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Sep 23 NS (Box 16, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 54-57.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Sep 30 NS (Box 16, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 57-60.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Oct 15 NS (Box 16, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 64-68.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Oct 23 NS (Box 16, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 75-78.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Oct 30 NS (Box 16, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 84-88.
      With enclosure: Bookseller's advertisement for Gualtieri's Index testarum conchyliorum.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Nov 6 NS (Box 16, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 92-94.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Nov 13 NS (Box 16, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 97-99.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Nov 20 NS (Box 16, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 99-101.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Nov 27 NS (Box 16, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 105-9.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Dec 11 NS (Box 16, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 109-17.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1742 Dec 18 NS (Box 16, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 119-22.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Jan 1 NS (Box 16, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 125-29.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Jan 7 NS (Box 16, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 132-35.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Jan 22 NS (Box 16, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 138-40.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Jan 29 NS (Box 16, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 144-47.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Feb 12 NS (Box 16, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 149-58.
      With enclosure: Copy of Theodore's edict.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Feb 18 NS (Box 16, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 159-65.
      With enclosure: Extract from a letter from Parma to Braitwitz, 10 Feb. 1743 NS; Copy of letter from Traun to Craon, 11 Feb. 1743 NS.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Feb 26 NS (Box 16, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 168-76.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Mar 5 NS (Box 16, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 176-79.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Mar 12 NS (Box 16, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 181-84.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Mar 19 NS (Box 16, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 186-90.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Mar 26 NS (Box 16, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 194-97.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Apr 2 NS (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 197-200.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Apr 15 or 22 NS (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 204-8.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Apr 30 NS (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 211-17.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 May 7 NS (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 221-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 May 21 NS (Box 17, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 226-30.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 May 28 NS (Box 17, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 233-36.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Jun 4 NS (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 238-41.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Jun 11 NS (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 241-44.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Jun 25 NS (Box 17, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 251-54.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Jul 2 NS (Box 17, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 256-57.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Jul 9 NS (Box 17, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 261-64.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Jul 23 NS (Box 17, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 269-71.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Jul 27 NS (Box 17, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 272-74.
    - Letter from John Chute to Horace Walpole, with a postscript from Horace Mann to Horace Walpole, 1743 Jul 29 NS (Box 17, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 275.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Aug 6 NS (Box 17, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 278-82.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Aug 13 NS (Box 17, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 284-87.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Aug 20 NS (Box 17, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 287-91.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Sep 3 NS (Box 17, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 294-97.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Sep 17 NS (Box 17, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 299-304.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Sep 24 NS (Box 17, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 307-10.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Oct 1 NS (Box 17, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 312-14.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Oct 15 NS (Box 17, Folder 22)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 321-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Oct 22 NS (Box 17, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 324-25.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Oct 27 NS (Box 17, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 328-31.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Nov 12 NS (Box 17, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 331-37.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Nov 19 NS (Box 17, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 337-40.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Dec 3 NS (Box 17, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 343-47.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Dec 10 NS (Box 17, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 347-48.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Dec 17 NS (Box 17, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 352-54.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1743 Dec 31 NS (Box 17, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 358-62.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Jan 5 NS (Box 17, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 362-64.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Jan 14 NS (Box 17, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 368-71.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Jan 21 NS (Box 17, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 371-74.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Jan 22 NS (Box 17, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 374-75.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Jan 28 NS (Box 17, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 376-81.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Feb 4 NS (Box 17, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 384-89.
      With enclosure: An account in Italian of the Young Pretender's departure from Rome. The letter from Mann to Walpole was written as a postscript to this account.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Feb 18 NS (Box 17, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 389-92.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Feb 25 NS (Box 17, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 394-98.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Mar 10 NS (Box 17, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 403-6.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Mar 17 NS (Box 17, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 411-16.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Mar 31 NS (Box 17, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 417-22.
      With enclosure: Excerpta quaedam ex antiquissimo MS codice.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Apr 7 NS (Box 17, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 425-28.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Apr 28 NS (Box 17, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 433-37.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 May 6 NS (Box 17, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 437-40.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 May 19 NS (Box 17, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 442-45.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Jun 2 NS (Box 17, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 445-48.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Jun 16 NS (Box 17, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 452-56.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Jun 23 NS (Box 17, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 459-62.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Jul 17 NS (Box 17, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 469-76.
      With enclosures: Copy of a letter from Horace Mann to Lobkowitz, 13 July 1744 NS; Copy of a letter from Horace Mann to Robert Long, 13 July 1744 NS.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Jul 21 NS (Box 17, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 476-79.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Aug 4 NS (Box 17, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 483-86.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Aug 16 NS (Box 17, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 486-94.
      With enclosures: Copy of a letter from Alexandre Albani to Horace Mann, 13 Aug. 1744 NS; Extract of a letter from the camp at Nemi, 12 Aug. 1744 NS; A list of captured Spanish and Neapolitan officers.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Sep 1 NS (Box 17, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 502-4.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Sep 22 NS (Box 17, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 506-8.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Sep 29 NS (Box 17, Folder 55)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 508-10.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Oct 6 NS (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 511-14.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Oct 13 NS (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 514-17.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Oct 27 NS (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 519-21.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Nov 10 NS (Box 18, Folder 4)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 525-27.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Nov 24 NS (Box 18, Folder 5)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 529-34.
      With enclosure: An account in French of the retreat of Lobkowitz's army.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Dec 8 NS (Box 18, Folder 6)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 541-45.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1744 Dec 22 NS (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 546-49.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Jan 5 NS (Box 18, Folder 8)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 553-56.
      Enclosure: A cutting from the Gazzetta di Mantova, 11 Dec. 1744 NS.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Jan 12 NS (Box 18, Folder 9)
      Yale Edition, v. 18, p. 557-60.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Jan 26 NS (Box 18, Folder 10)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 1-3.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Feb 16 NS (Box 18, Folder 11)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 6-9.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Mar 9 NS (Box 18, Folder 12)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 9-15.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Mar 23 NS (Box 18, Folder 13)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 21.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Apr 6 NS (Box 18, Folder 14)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 21-24.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Apr 20 NS (Box 18, Folder 15)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 29-31.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 May 4 NS (Box 18, Folder 16)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 34-38.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 May 18 NS (Box 18, Folder 17)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 40-42.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 May 25 NS (Box 18, Folder 18)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 46-48.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Jun 1 NS (Box 18, Folder 19)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 48-52.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Jun 15 NS (Box 18, Folder 20)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 54-56.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Jun 29 NS (Box 18, Folder 21)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 56-59.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Jul 13 NS (Box 18, Folder 22)
      With enclosure: Copy of Lomellini's letter to Schulemberg, 29 June 1745 NS.
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 64-67.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Jul 27 NS (Box 18, Folder 23)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 75-77.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Aug 10 NS (Box 18, Folder 24)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 79-86.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Aug 17 NS (Box 18, Folder 25)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 86-90.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Aug 24 NS (Box 18, Folder 26)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 93-95.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Aug 31 NS (Box 18, Folder 27)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 95-97.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Sep 7 NS (Box 18, Folder 28)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 98-101.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Copy in George Giberne's hand), 1745 Sep 20 OS (Box 18, Folder 29)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 108-12.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Oct 5 NS (Box 18, Folder 30)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 112-15.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Oct 12 NS (Box 18, Folder 31)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 119-25.
      With enclosure: Copy of a letter from San Remo, 5 Oct. 1745 NS.
    - Letter from Horace Walpole (Copy in George Giberne's hand), 1745 Oct 4 OS (Box 18, Folder 32)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 125-29.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Oct 19 NS (Box 18, Folder 33)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 130-32.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Oct 26 NS (Box 18, Folder 34)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 135-37.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Nov 9 NS (Box 18, Folder 35)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 140-45.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Nov 10 NS (Box 18, Folder 36)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 145-52.
      With enclosure: List of toasts drunk at a dinner at Leghorn.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Nov 23 NS (Box 18, Folder 37)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 155-58.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Nov 30 NS (Box 18, Folder 38)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 162-65.
      With enclosure: Copy of Rivarola's letter from Bastia, 24 Nov. 1745.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Dec 7 NS (Box 18, Folder 39)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 169-72.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1745 Dec 21 NS (Box 18, Folder 40)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 182-85.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Jan 4 NS (Box 18, Folder 41)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 190-92.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Jan 18 NS (Box 18, Folder 42)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 196-97.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Jan 25 NS (Box 18, Folder 43)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 197-200.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Feb 15 NS (Box 18, Folder 44)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 205-7.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Mar 1 NS (Box 18, Folder 45)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 214-16.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Mar 15 NS (Box 18, Folder 46)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 217-21.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Mar 22 NS (Box 18, Folder 47)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 225-28.
      With enclosure: Transcript of a paper transmitted to the Comte de Sale; Transcript of a letter from Rome to Goldsworthy.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Apr 5 NS (Box 18, Folder 48)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 230-32.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Apr 19 NS (Box 18, Folder 49)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 235-39.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Apr 26 NS (Box 18, Folder 50)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 244-46.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 May 7 NS (Box 18, Folder 51)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 251.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 May 24 NS (Box 18, Folder 52)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 252-54.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 May 31 NS (Box 18, Folder 53)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 256-59.
      With enclosures: Two cuttings from an Italian newspaper, containing an article dated Versailles 6 May on affairs in Scotland.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Jun 14 NS (Box 18, Folder 54)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 260-63.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Jun 21 NS (Box 18, Folder 55)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 265-68.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Jun 28 NS (Box 18, Folder 56)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 268-71.
      With enclosure: List of captured material and of casualties incurred in the battle of Piacenza.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Jul 19 NS (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Yale Edition, v. 19, p. 275-77.
    - Letter to Horace Walpole, 1746 Aug 9 NS (Box 19, Folder 2)